this strip fatigue
esta tira la fatiga que
what's up my kids well today is a
qué pasa mi chavalería bueno hoy es un
very special day a very different video
día muy especial un vídeo muy diferente
than what I'm used to
a lo que estoy acostumbrado
and I'm bringing the tastiest black guy
y es que traigo al negrito más sabroso
on the internet the most playful black guy on
de internet al negrito más juguetón de
YouTube who is dedicated to exposing
youtube que se dedica a exponer la vida
people's sexual lives I said hey moto 20
sexual de la peña he dicho oye moto 20
over here let me put you in and what's up how
para acá que te ponga yo y qué pasa qué
is mister javi oliva
tal como está el señor javi oliva
thank you so much for coming it's a pleasure
muchísimas gracias por venir un placer
I really wanted to record something we've been
tenía muchísimas ganas de grabar algo
here for a long time not too
aquí estamos hace mucho tiempo no hace
long ago but I wanted to be on
mucho tiempo pero me quería yo estar en
this channel it's full of respect now for me
este canal es es full respeto ya para mí
this gives you respect fear no respect
esto te da respeto miedo no nos respecto
from here I see this when it's
desde aquí yo esto lo veo cuando editó
always edited I mean I put it on like this
siempre o sea yo me lo pongo tal
hahaha one of the questions you were leaving is ahead of time
jajaja está adelantada una de las
calm down a little
preguntas que te ibas cálmate un poco
black guy forgive me forgive me my friend but
negrito perdóname perdona mi amigo pero
well I'm bringing you a little salt I know or
bueno te traigo un poquito de sal se o
a little bit of sexuality and a little bit of
un poquito de sexualidad y un poquito de
what your people like I hope you do
lo que le gusta a tu gente yo espero que
n't have any qualms about answering anything no
no tenga reparo en contestar a nada no
let's go let's as we came to play
let's go let como hemos venido a jugar
we came to play very well said there's a
hemos venido a jugar muy bien dicho
lot to  start a little without
haber mucho para empezar un poquito sin
soft I wanted to ask you what type of
suave quería preguntarte qué tipo de
content you consume on the internet I
contenido consume tú en internet yo
consume a lot I
consumo mucho
consume you a lot the most in this
os consumo mucho a ti el que más en este
area to the south and such but I also consume a
ámbito al sur y tal pero consumo también
lot at 8 I consume at Portillo I don't consume
mucho a 8 consumo a portillo no consumo
like a niche consumption to people with
como un nicho de consumo a personas con
the 8 what uploads I see Portillo what
las 8 lo que sube lo veo portillo lo que
uploads I see and Le Havre or what uploads I
sube lo veo y le havre o lo que sube lo
also think they are the only three
veo también creo que son las únicas tres
people who upload what they add I see and
personas que suban lo que suman lo veo y
then there are people like you who
luego ya estáis gente como tú que me
accompany me in my days as a bearable
acompañéis en mis días como llevadero
plan I put on Javi and I continue on my path
plan me pongo a javi y sigo mi camino
but those three are what I consume the
pero esos tres es lo que consumo los
others are there is the falsetto it's cool
demás están ahí está el falsete mola
yes there are times that I don't know what you're talking about that's why I
si hay veces que no sé de qué habláis
know that I like it because there are times that I do
por eso sé que me mola porque hay veces
n't know what you're talking about but I
que no sé de qué habláis pero me lo
put it on
pongo
[Music]
[Música]
why did you send me a message giving me
por qué me mandaste un mensaje dándome
support for a thing and that's the
apoyo de una movida y eso s la movida de
summer thing yes but I had already been following you for
verano sí pero ya te llevaba siguiendo
a while for that it was like look
bastante para eso fue en plan de mira
Javi knows I exist but I'd been
javi sabe que existo pero ya llevaba
like two years or what do you do  you put it
igual dos años o si haces tú te lo pones
like a radio plan the grain is almost like a
como en plan radio el grano es casi como
podcast exactly one of the questions I
podcast exacto una de las preguntas que
had for you and then we'll go
tenía para ti y luego iremos más
further hey to [ __ ] they play music it
adelante oye para [__] te ponen música
doesn't play it for you then here it occurs to me to
no te la pone entonces aquí se me ocurre
ask I would put on a podcast by javi
preguntar te pondría un podcast de javi
oliveira from jabil canijo to
oliveira de jabil canijo para que te
accompany you but it seems a little murky to me
acompañe pero me parece un poco turbia
the debt listen to me I'm
la deuda escúchame
not deceiving my father I'm not going to
no engaño a mi padre yo no te voy a
deny that it may have happened without wanting to
negar que igual ha pasado sin querer
like martin we want them to be
como martín queremos que me están
loving me and with this let's see as a family
queriendo y con esto a ver en familia
listen to me maybe I put it on to sleep
escúchame igual me lo pongo para dormir
and one thing leads to another maybe you're
y una cosa lleva a otra cosa igual estás
there on my phone maybe you're there I
ahí en mi móvil igual estás ahí yo no
wasn't in agreement
estaba de acuerdo
I will talk to my girlfriend but I was going to be
hablaré con mi novia pero iba a estar
out in many places this is
fuera en muchos sitios esto es una
proof of that it doesn't destroy many
prueba de ello no destruye muchos sitios
strange places that I don't know that one like
extraños que desconozco ese como
jesus christ and let yourself see how far I
jesucristo y déjate fíjate hasta dónde
can go they can't in case there is
puedo llegar no pueden por si hay
someone who has lived nobody has
alguien que ha vivido nadie nos ha
found out the last habit was the last
enterado el último hábito fue el último
habit until we are recording in
hábito hasta que estamos grabando de
fact it was the one in dallas of fear at the
hecho ha sido el de dallas de miedo a la
gala has had a lot of problem a lot with
gala ha tenido mucho problema mucho con
this video I tell you  that I was looking at
este vídeo te digo que yo estaba mirando
the bar the whole time and one read
todo el rato la barra y uno leía
comments looked at the light bar and
comentarios miraba la barra de lights y
this light and the like bar the
this light y la barra de likes la
first half hour has almost the
primera media hora tiene casi el récord
channel record the like the like has in the
del canal el like el likes tiene en la
first hour has almost the
primera hora tiene casi el récord del
channel record only koski and christina surpass it
canal sólo le superan koski y christina
immigration bad accept or no no no no no no
inmigración mal acepta o no no no no no
no but of course in the end there is that thing of you
no no pero claro al final está eso de
know the comments I can't
que sabes los comentarios yo no los
control them or anything and in the
puedo controlar ni nada y en los
comments there are atrocities there
comentarios hay barbaridades
are atrocities but it's what I tell you they
hay barbaridades pero es lo que te digo
always highlight the 200
siempre resaltan los 200 comentarios
bad comments to all the good ones and they are the ones that
malos a todos los que hay buenos y son
have the likes having
los que tienen los likes haber
collaborated with many people who have a
colaborado con mucha gente que le tiene
lot in the ring of course that is the problem
mucho en el aro claro ese es el problema
but of course you see the global you say the
pero claro tú ves el global tú dices el
global and today you can see the
global y a día de hoy lo podéis ver los
likes and it has that video which is an
likes y tiene ese vídeo que es una
outrage it is a real outrage
barbaridad es una verdadera barbaridad
one thing that does not escape me to moto let's
una cosa que a mí no se me escapa a moto
see you know that I get involved in everything it does
a ver tú sabes que yo metido en todo a
not go away for me no zinc stands out
mí no se me va a una no despunta el zinc
and normally normally not always
y lo normalmente normalmente no siempre
when you make a habit give an
cuando tú haces un hábito da una
opportunity that someone you  ask you
oportunidad que alguien te pregunte a ti
there we are okay you know where I'm going I do
ahí estamos vale ya saben por dónde voy
n't know where this one goes I commented the
no sé por dónde va este comentó yo los
moments here what happened Dallas
momentos aquí lo que ocurrió dallas me
asked me a question and what happens if I
hizo una pregunta a mí y qué pasa si yo
answered it was very difficult no no no no no no no it was
le respondí era muy chunga no no no no
very difficult it's just that we
no no no era muy chunga solo que nos
went on so long that two things happened
alargamos tanto que pasaban dos cosas
leaving the question halfway was worse than
dejar la pregunta a medias era peor que
what I did because it was a question like
lo que hice porque era una pregunta en
if everything that had to be talked about
plan si de todo lo que había que hablar
in that question was going to be too
en esa pregunta iba a quedar demasiado
long and it was going to go off a lot of what
largo y se iba a salir mucho de lo que
are habits in general then I
es hábitos en general entonces a mí me
would love to do I don't know where
encantaría volver a hacer no sé en dónde
another move with her talk about that topic
otra movida con ella hablar de ese tema
because I want to talk about that topic I
porque yo quiero hablar de ese tema yo
'm not a turkey of no no no no it
no soy un pavo de no no no no sólo que
was just the same 8 minutes in that answer and it
era igual 8 minutos en esa respuesta y
was how I go and I don't want to cut look
era como voy y no quiero cortar mira
I want to take away a lot of curiosity now
quiero quitarle a mucha curiosidad ahora
you know what I ask you if you want the
sabes que te pregunto si quieres la
question from Dallas was attentive people what do you
pregunta de dallas fue atento gente qué
think of my current controversy that's
opinas de mi polémica actual que me está
happening to me now it wasn't sexual no no no no
pasando ahora no era sexual no no no no
no we are talking 8 minutes okay it
no estamos hablando 8 minutos vale que
can be any question it's 16 and
puede ser cualquier pregunta es 16 y
well you have to make a video with that
pues tienes que hacer un vídeo con eso
exists and you  think that I have the
existe y tú piensa que yo tengo el vídeo
entire video as a scoop I'm telling you the
entero como primicia te digo el hábitos
Dallas habits lasted 28 minutes and 35
de dallas duraba 28 minutos y 35
seconds the raw doesn't give us everything already well
segundos el bruto no nos da todo ya bien
edited and everything the extended version today
editado y todo la versión extendida hoy
has many problems to monetize your
tiene muchos problemas para monetizar tu
channel yes but I do tactics do you accept
canal sí pero hago tácticas aceptas
girl would they get wet in saying if you want and you do
chica se mojarían en decir si quieres y
n't want to go I would get wet say what
no quieres ir yo te mojarían decir cuál
is the maximum that has generated only
es el máximo que ha generado solamente
with visits from YouTube in a video or in
con visitas de youtube en un vídeo o en
a month in a month what I generated in
un mes en un mes lo que genere yo en
November almost the month that the most was generated
noviembre casi el mes que más se generan
was eight thousand nine hundred euros that is
fueron ocho mil novecientos euros eso es
the maximum yes yes a lot
lo máximo sí sí mucho vídeo amarillo ahí
of yellow video there not expensive expensive expensive a lot of yellow on top of that it was a month that Christi ninis had big people at that time but I generated 8,900 payments but that was a lot of yellow in the end people say not always but in reality it is the best month the best in November 6 milestone I swear it is
bueno en noviembre 6 hito lo juro es
literally what people always
literalmente lo de la gente siempre
say and always but I don't know if you have
dicen y siempre pero no sé si tiene
the phone at hand to tell me what
el móvil a mano para decirme cuáles son
the statistics are of your channel's audience, I
las estadísticas de la audiencia de tu
mean I mean percentage of
canal o sea quiero decir porcentaje de
men, women and age
hombres de mujeres y de edad
of men  it's brutal it's what I wanted to
de hombres es brutal es lo que quería
know about men exaggerated about men
saber de hombres exagerado de hombres
exaggerate okay statistics from my channel
exagera vale estadísticas de mi canal
man 92 3% and I'm the serious one out of a million
hombre 92 3% y yo el serio de un millón
and a half not a million and a half that exist
y pico no un millón y medio que existís
92.3 percent age the one that most 18 24 25
92.3 por ciento edad la que más 18 24 25
percentage of men are half very
porcentaje de hombres son medios muy
crazy mine is impressive but in
locos lo mío es impresionante pero en
the 90s and so it won't fit in there's no way there's
los 90 y tanto no meterá ni de coña
been 92 with 3 I only know one person who
habido 92 con 3 sólo conozco una persona
beats me in men only one person
que me ganan en hombres sólo una persona
that there's someone who does you only one
que hay alguien que te haga sólo una
person who is with knows she's the only one
persona que es con sabe la es la única
who surpasses me that I know in person
que me supera que yo conozca en persona
and Spain I'm 68 with 9 then Argentina
y españa tengo 68 con 9 luego argentina
then Mexico logo Chile I polo going
luego méxico logo chile yo polo
back a bit to the subject well going back
volviendo un poco al tema pues volviendo
a bit to the subject of Dallas and putting
un poco al tema de dallas y metiendo
noria a bit to the next to the
noria un poco a la siguiente al
next tone of the interview if
siguiente tono de la entrevista si te
the opportunity arose and you had to
surgiera la oportunidad y tuvieras que
choose a partner to have
elegir a un compañero con el que hacer
a threesome with who would you choose sadhal wow and
un trío a quién elegiría sadhalá guau y
michu and because it's very good
michu y porque es muy bueno
now I understand people when they're on
ahora entiendo a la gente cuando está en
this side I think like I don't know  how is it to
este lado creo como no sé cómo es
know how lass enters I can talk
el saber cómo entra lass puedo hablar
to him like a joke look we do this
con él en plan broma mira hacemos una
thing like you last a long time in bed
cosa como tu duras mucho en la cama
let me do my techniques at first and
déjame al principio hacer mis técnicas y
then you give it to him because you can handle it I
luego tú le das caña porque tú aguanta
think I could talk to him like we were
yo creo que podría hablar con él en plan
born this type of mobility
rollo de nacemos este tipo de movilidad
such or rather because I saw complicity or rather
tal o sea porque yo vi complicidad o sea
each place in bed I think we are
cada sitio en la cama creo que somos
really compatible from Dallas and you're
compatibles de verdad de dallas y estás
seeing this today then a person who
viendo esto hoy entonces una persona que
well he has said more than once that
bueno él ha dicho más de una ocasión que
you can see yourself one day collaborating with win michelle the next day with us it's more it happened it happened in a week in fact to happen this week if there is someone that you have collaborated with lately with that I've seen a range of variety in
visto un abanico de variedad en
collaborations is there someone that has
colaboraciones hay alguien que te haya
surprised you for good for good 8 it's
sorprendido para bien para bien 8 es
better than I expected when you admire
mejor de lo que esperaba cuando admiras
someone you know that you're very scared
a alguien sabes que tienes mucho miedo
so it was like look man I want to
entonces fue como mira tío que quiero
do a new section you have to
hacer una nueva sección te tienes que
download this app please such as me who
descargar esta app por favor tal yo que
only follows 70 people and who reacts to
sólo sigue a 70 personas y que reacciona
a video I said it's time and he saw me he
un vídeo me dije es el momento y me vio
saw me and accepted and from there he even told
me vio y aceptó y de ahí hasta me dijo a
me to go out in  your channel that I swear we
mí para salir en su canal que lo juro
were super surprised and without very
estábamos súper sorprendidos y sin muy
cool and for bad for bad
guay y para mal para mal
someone who has surprised me for bad
alguien que me ha sorprendido para mal
yet nobody I need a little more for
todavía nadie necesito un poco más para
bad to see you know what you say but
mal para ver sabes eso de que dices pero
maybe I had a bad day I still can't
igual tenía un día malo todavía no te
tell you return a question and here
puedo decir regresar una pregunta y aquí
you are going to demonstrate your attitude with this
vas a demostrar tu actitud con esta
interview when it comes to showing this
entrevista a la hora de mostrar esto
okay don't [ __ ] with me let's see how I formulate it
vale no me jodas a ver cómo la formuló
because I don't want more I denounce pigtails it has
porque no quiero más denunció a coletas
fatigue what
tiene a la fatiga qué
yes
sí
d I don't
d
believe it I have
no me la creo
not answered it
yo no me la he respondido
making the content that we do torio
haciendo el contenido que hacemos torio
I imagine that on many occasions let's see we
me imagino que en muchas ocasiones a ver
are humans not the current body how it
somos humanos no el cuerpo actual cómo
acts no as for occasions you have
actúa no en cuanto a ocasiones te has
almost had a cookie after
tenido casi una galleta después de
finishing recording look this is
terminar de grabar fíjate que esto es
funny because at the moment like I am
gracioso porque en el momento como estoy
now with you I don't care if possible it is not the same,
ahora contigo me da igual si cabe no es
I am not the same Javier and look at
lo mismo yo no lo mismo javier y mira
Gemma Wizard not expensive I do not
que gemma wizard no caros
count when I am editing the
no lo cuento cuando estoy editando me
same thing happens to me I am editing and I say [ __ ] what a
pasa igual estoy editando y digo [__]
move edit made one avoid that
que movida editar hecho uno evitar eso
listen to me that when I was editing those
hazme caso que cuando editaba esas
things you say and if you are listening to see
movidas dices y si está escuchando a ver
canine in the background even worse  and that is so is
canino de fondo ya peor aún y eso es así
that you think it's a joke I didn't edit
es que tú creo que es broma no editaba
gem wifi contiguous and talking I like it
gema wifi contigua y hablando me gusta
calms me down and then it gives me a
me tranquiliza y entonces me da una
good feeling is there someone a lot with
buena sensación hay alguien montón con
which today you stay with the
la que a día de hoy te quedes con las
desire to take your channel to a habit
ganas de llevar a tu canal a un hábito
apart from this deposit the deposits do you
aparte de este depósito los depósitos lo
see it possible I really don't see it possible
ves posible realmente no lo veo posible
but he liked the photo that was uploaded
pero le dio like a la foto que subía
hell if he is doing it there are some
infierno si lo está haciendo hay unas
techniques I don't see it possible on the one
técnicas yo no lo veo posible por un
hand I tried seeing the resistance but
lado intenté vista la resistencia pero
I don't want to take him either I want to
tampoco yo quiero llevarle yo lo quiero
take him because people want me to go
llevar porque la gente quiere que vaya
so it's like a gift but of course I
entonces es como regalo pero claro yo
always said that the person I
siempre dije que la persona que yo
wanted to take a habit will be 8 and I still have
quería llevar un hábito será 8 y todavía
n't taken him but now I know that I can
no lo he llevado pero ahora sé que puedo
do it so now that I can take
hacerlo entonces ahora que puedo llevar
look well I would really like to
a mira pues de verdad me gustaría de
really have a plan to take and it's not because I'm
verdad un plan llevar y no es porque sea
big but I would like to take the
grande sino que me gustaría llevar al
blonde roll of host not because of the visits
rubio royo de [__] no por las visitas
I swear it's because even I want to
se lo juro es porque hasta yo quiero
know I think if I pay it has to be
saber yo creo que sí pago tiene que ser
super pay that you tell him don't see I'm going to
súper pago que le digas no vea voy a
do some techniques and I'm going to leave you with
hacer unas técnicas y te voy a dejar con
a super saiyan you will have a fetish
una super saiyan tendrás un fetiche
me too I do it too  I think
yo también yo también lo creo
apart from not being interested in visiting
aparte de no es por interés por visitar
slightly out of modesty projects
proyectos ligeramente fuera modestia no
you don't need that it's basically
te hace falta eso es básicamente es
because it gives me uncertainty that plan of
porque me da incertidumbre ese plan de
techniques in Andorra is better done the
técnicas en andorra se hace mejor el
sixth and objective of those questions in the
sexto y objetivo de esos preguntas en la
mountain with friendship to the mountain no the
montaña con la amistad al monte no la
goat pulls for the mountain
cabra tira para el monte
hey I was checking your channel a little
oye estaba revisando un poco tu canal
today not before before meeting you
hoy no antes de antes de quedar contigo
and your most viewed video caught my attention
y me llama la atención tu vídeo más
I was expecting it to be your
visto sea me esperaba que se fuera tu
most viewed video is the device if I'm not
vídeo más visto está el device si no me
mistaken no and then it
equivoco no y luego
's fake it's a short that I made with the
es falso es un corto que hice con el
school
colegio
when I studied film at school it was
cuando estudiaba cine al colegio era
like we had to try to recreate
como que teníamos que intentar recrear
something in real life and upload it and I said
algo en la vida real y subirlo y yo dije
can I do it on my YouTube channel the
puedo hacerlo en mi canal de youtube lo
same as yes yes yes it is recorded and the
mismo que si si si se graba y la
teacher told me but you have to
profesora me decía pero tienes que
create it in a way that even I
crearlo de una forma que hasta yo me lo
believed they gave me a 10 and then I
creí me pusieron un 10 y luego ese vídeo
really uploaded that video and it didn't work that
de verdad lo subí y no funcionó ese
video didn't work like that now time that's I do
vídeo no funcionó así ahora el tiempo
n't understand anything that video until
eso es no entiendo nada ese vídeo hasta
two years later suddenly one
dos años después de repente en una
Christmas he asked me on one Christmas he gave me
navidad me pidió en una navidad me dio
two million points million and said that
dos millones puntos millones y dijo que
the positive side that helps the girl
el lado positivo que ayuda a la muchacha
but it also has a negative side the
pero tiene también lado negativo el
scare that gives the kid of course expensive
susto que le pega al chaval claro caro
Carlos all fictions of trade I'm not
carlos todo ficciones de oficio no soy
that type of [ __ ] or make love
ese tipo de [__] o hacer el amor
[ __ ] this is already a little bit like
[__] esto ya es un poco a los
monsters papi purists and [ __ ] [ __ ]
monstruos papi puristas y [__] [__]
yes no jokes in team sex with or without
sí sin bromas en team sexo con o sin
music with music with the week there like
música con música con the week en ahí en
the wicker the weekend and the
plan the wicker the weekend and the caso
Javier Tovar case in notes day or night
javier tovar en notas de día o de noche
at night and more if it can be at dawn
de noche y más si puede ser de madrugada
already at the hours that you finish the live such and
ya a las horas que acabas del directo
such will also know it will be that I'm
tal también sabrá será que me estoy
getting older but when it catches me
haciendo mayor pero cuando me coge
sincerely when I was young it was the
sinceramente cuando estaba joven era la
night
noche
at dawn
por la madrugada pero ahora para mí la
but now for me the best time is the morning the day will start waking up okay okay I also buy it there are people who like it very good very good also that when I tell you in the morning it's almost a nap I don't know what we're talking about in video he showed it
estamos hablando en vídeo de mostró
clear clear that the sev forgotten
claro claro que la sev olvidadas
forgotten by work ahead
olvidados por de trabajo por delante por
ahead I think that it is overrated
delante yo creo que está sobrevalorado
the behind I think that from my point
el por detrás yo creo que desde mi punto
of view I think that clear and when things are
de creo que claro y cuando las cosas se
designed they are for a reason it is not like that
diseñan son para algo no es así
things are  made for what they are
las cosas están hechas para lo que están
made then yes you should only innovate it
hechas ya luego si sólo deberás innovar
is your business its part the ass no yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes totally not
es cosa tuya su parte el culo no sí sí
totally like roll that they open it for me
totalmente en plan rollo que me lo abran
like very cessation of the sea and to the last
cual muy cese del mar y a la última
question this one is really complicated I
pregunta ésta sí que complicada
needed we have now I am afraid of
necesitaba tenemos ahora le tengo miedo
hours but such things in life
horas pero tales cosas de la vida
imagine that it arises to you okay if it
imagínate que te surge vale si te
arises to you and you had the opportunity to
surgiera y tuvieras la oportunidad a
whom have I asked several the penis of Pablo
quien le hecho varias el pene a pablo
Iglesia quite something Abascal I think
iglesia bastante algo abascal yo creo
that Abascal sucked Xanthi's penis
que abascal le chupó el pene al xanthi
I think he is a doctor a payment that
yo creo que es un médico un pago que
smells like Brummel and such a trance it would be like
huele a brummel y tal trance sería como
a clean penis and he knew it a
un pene limpios y lo supo hace un
little while ago such and then I tell him well he threw me you
poquito tal y luego le digo bueno me
know a plan done my work and I'm
tiró sabes un plan hecho mi trabajo y me
leaving yes yes I think it is a clean penis
voy sí sí yo creo que es un pene limpio
I liked clean hair but yes I
me ha gustado el pelo limpio pero sí yo
think he has a clean penis 6 like
creo que tiene un pene limpio 6 en plan
a penis that sucks it yes it smells good it smells
un pene que lo chupa sí huele bien huele
a little like first he compared a Gandhi such
un poco a primero comparó un gandhi tal
I think of my genius do you have any
pienso en mi genio tienes alguna
questions prepared for me the truth is
pregunta preparada para mí la verdad es
that not
que no
the same anything can happen
lo mismo puede ocurrir cualquier cosa
if you know that  I really liked a
si tú sabes que me gustaba mucho una
section of yours on your channel where you did
sección tuya de tu canal que hacías
interviews. Do you think I could ever
entrevista algún día crees que podría
see it as a regular session again? I
volver a ver como sesión fija lo dudo
highly doubt it, man. First of all, for
muchísimo tío en primer lugar que para
my channel it's not very beneficial because at the
mi canal no es muy beneficioso porque al
end of the day they are commitments. Then no,
fin y al cabo son compromisos luego no
because you have to be a little
porque tienes que estar un poco
grateful. Also, when someone reaches out to you, there's
agradecido también cuando te tiende la
no such thing as a sixth and they offer to
mano no existe la sexta y se ofrecen a
appear on your channel, then it makes you a
salir en tu canal luego te hace ser un
little less objective when it comes to
poco menos objetivo a la hora de
commenting on something. You never
comentar una movida que haya no nunca
know who might have a love and
sabes quién puede tener un amor y de
who not. And then it was also
quién no y luego aparte también era era
quite a pain in the sense that
bastante [__] en el sentido de que
you have to be behind people.
tienes que estar detrás de la gente
Now, yes, do it. It's not a bit of a
ahora sí haga no es un poco poner en el
commitment. You know, and it seems that I don't have
compromiso a la gente sabe y como que no
the need to be
tengo la necesidad tampoco de andar
behind anyone either. I like some things that I
detrás de nadie me gusta alguna cosa que
like. I really like collaborating, for
me gusta me gusta mucho colaborar por
example, right now I'm here with you for a
ejemplo ahora estoy aquí contigo hecho
while but I'm having a really good time. I like it,
rato pero estoy pasando muy bien me
especially live when
gusta sobre todo en directo cuando
we do the debates. I'm afraid one day
hacemos los debates me teme un día y que
you'll get bored. In fact, we've
te aburres mi mente de hecho lo hemos
talked about it and I like it, but as a
hablado y me gusta pero como sección
regular section, you won't know what? No, I'm still waiting for
fija no sabrás qué no yo sigo esperando
a good interview, how are they? But what about the
una buena entrevista cómo está pero anda
6th face?  day that happens
las de 6to face el día que eso pase
internet or was good
internet o fue bueno
[Music]
[Música]
but an interview like I see
pero una entrevista rollo que vea
interviews of the 50 minutes and 12
entrevistas de los 50 minutos y 12
seconds
segundos
palomas well it has been a
palomas bueno pues ha sido toda una
wonder to have you here totally
maravilla tener de por aquí totalmente
my gentleman and you know that here
caballero mío y que sepas que aquí me
you have to make me angry because still
tienes que dar rabia porque todavía
nobody, I mean yes there is someone who has been
nadie o sea sí que hay alguien que me ha
able to criticize me or such and I would like to
podido criticar o tal y me gustaría
talk but still as there is not only I will
hablar pero todavía como no hay sólo te
tell you as a final move that already o cabrera
diré como movida final que ya o cabrera
sent a md to do some
envió un md para hacer unos equis
balls
[__]
to me too and also a super
a mí también y también una cosa súper
strange thing not a thing of the cabrera now he
rara no una cosa de la cabrera ahora me
sent it to me directly but importing
lo mandó directamente si no importando a
someone from his group but come on that will be
alguien de su grupo pero vamos eso será
if it was a roll in fact I think darlas
si era un rollo de hecho creo que darlas
exposed it with the cup how lucky the
lo expuso con la copa lo suerte la
thing and it was basically that as a complaint they
movida y era básicamente que como queja
make an Instagram account that
que hagan cuenta de instagram a que
appeared or they provided them but
aparecía o las proporcionaban ellos pero
that the result was not what they were
que el resultado no era lo que estaban
selling and nothing man thank you very much it was
vendiendo y nada tío muchísimas gracias
a pleasure I
mostró todo un placer de verdad te lo
tell you and that live chat is pending
digo y queda pendiente esa charla en
totally worth it gentlemen a
directo valer totalmente caballeros un
hug people a kiss and follow this
abrazo gente un beso y seguid a este
man who will help you a lot in life
hombre que os ayudará mucho en la vida
When you are sad, there are totally
cuando estéis tristes existen totalmente
quite recommendable ones.
bastante recomendable